Welcome to NudgeAI - A Proactive Personal Assistant
Today, I'll walk you through NudgeAI, a cutting-edge proactive personal assistant that unifies your calendar, location, and Drive data to help you achieve your goals.
NudgeAI features a sophisticated multi-layered architecture. The frontend is built with React and Vite, providing a modern dashboard interface.
The backend uses Python with FastAPI, while the RAG system handles semantic search and AI processing. The MCP server enables integration with Hugging Face models.
The frontend dashboard provides real-time insights into your calendar events, recent documents, location history, and health statistics.
It connects to the backend API to fetch and display your personal data in an organized, actionable format.
The MCP server exposes powerful tools for querying your data. You can search calendar events, location history, and Drive documents.
It also provides habit analysis and personal insights by combining multiple data sources with AI processing.
The RAG system enables semantic search across all your data. It uses vector embeddings to find relevant information and provides context-aware responses.
This allows for natural language queries like 'When can I meet John this week?' or 'How often do I miss the gym?'
A key innovation is the WhiteCircle integration, which provides quality gates to prevent hallucinations.
Before showing any response to you, the system checks for factual accuracy and automatically retries if issues are detected.
NudgeAI proactively suggests actions based on your context. It can recommend optimal gym times, remind you of missed habits.
And provide personalized insights to help you achieve your goals.
NudgeAI represents the future of personal assistants - privacy-first, self-healing, and truly context-aware.
It's designed to help you make better decisions and achieve your goals without compromising your data privacy.
NudgeAI: Your Proactive Partner for Better Decisions